chatwing.com 2015-09-14

# Privacy Policy of Web Services LLC

This privacy statement ("Privacy Policy") applies to the chatwing.com website ("Chatwing"), and all associated services provided in connection with chatwing including mobile (collectively, "Service") that are owned and operated by Web Services LLC. ("Web Services", "we", "us", "our").   
We take privacy matters very seriously and we are committed to protect your privacy.   
Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy. By visiting Chatwing, submitting information or using any of our Services, you are accepting the conditions outlined in this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use Agreement. 

**Information We Collect  
Information provided by you**   
We collect personal information, such as your email address and demographic data, when you register to become a member of Chatwing. As part of your personal profile, you may also choose to submit information such as your interests and photos. In addition to your profile information, we collect and archive all user materials that you post, including, but not limited to, chat messages. 

**Information collected automatically**   
We may receive and store certain types of non-personally identifiable information whenever you interact with us, including, without limitation, information that common web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the IP, browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each user request. Our purpose in collecting such information is to better understand how our users use Chatwing for the purpose of improving the Service and also monetization opportunities. 

**IP addresses**   
We do store IP addresses of all incoming connections to chatWING servers. This information is stored for security purposes such as preventing abuse or intrusion. When a user sends a message to a chatWING Group, the IP address of the sender is recorded and displayed to the group owner and to the group moderators created by the group owner, so that the group owner and moderators can ban the sender from the group. IP addresses contain no personal or confidential information. 

**Third Party Advertising**   
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies 

**Payment Information**   
We store payment information (credit card type, card holder's name, credit card expiration date, PayPal account email) for all payments and donations made to chatWING. Credit card numbers are not stored on our servers. This information is only used for security purposes, such as preventing fraudulent payments. 

**Cookies**   
A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a user's computer, and that the user's browser provides to the website each time the user returns. This is a widely used and common internet technology.   
We may use cookies to identify and quickly retrieve login information and provide data that we can use to improve our Service. Chatwing users who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Chatwing, with the understanding that certain features of Chatwing may not function properly. 

**Newsletter**   
Users who signup or login to the Chatwing services share the users email address with chatwing, including via any social media systems and networks such as Facebook, google, twitter, instagram and any other 3rd party services chatwing supports are automatically opt-in to any chatwing newsletter and email services including sharing your email with 3rd parties for potential monetization opportunities. 

**Disclosure and Use of information**   
Your profile information and posted materials, with the exception of your profile email address, will be viewable by other users of Chatwing. We may use your email address to inform you from time to time about new products or features, solicit feedback and may also use it for security reasons to confirm your provided information.   
We may use the information collected automatically, such as your IP address and information stored via cookies, to gather statistics about the number of people who visit Chatwing and to help us improve the Service. We may share this non-personally identifying information with third parties to better serve our users.   
Advertisements that appear on Chatwing are delivered to you by our advertising partners. We do not provide your email address to our advertising partners or third parties. We may, however, transfer information about your use of Chatwing, such as your IP address and information stored via cookies, to our advertising partners and other third parties. This information may be used to provide advertising, promotions and other products and services that may be of particular interest to you. It may also be used to provide you with a tailored choice of content.   
We will disclose your personally identifiable information if we reasonably believe we are required to do so by law, regulation or other government authority or to protect the rights and property of our company, its affiliates or the public. We may also co-operate with law enforcement agencies in any official investigation and we may disclose your personally identifiable information to the relevant agency or authority in doing so.   
We reserve the right to publish any request or feedback that you submit through email or other feedback mechanisms, in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users.   
We reserve the right to transfer your personal information in the event of a transfer of ownership of Chatwing, such as acquisition by or merger with another company. 

**Third Parties**   
This policy does not apply to the practices of third parties that we do not own or control, or to individuals that we do not employ or manage. Chatwing may contain links to other websites, and other websites may contain links to Chatwing. These other websites are not under our control. The privacy and security practices of websites linked to or from Chatwing are not covered by this Privacy Policy, and we are not responsible for the privacy or security practices or the content of such websites. 

**Security**   
We are committed to protecting your privacy and we take measures to ensure the privacy of your personal data. However, please be aware that no security measures are 100% secure or impenetrable. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. 

**No User Under Age 13**   
Chatwing does not allow any anyone under the age of 13 to use our Service. If you are under 13, please leave the site immediately. 

**User Between the Ages of 13 and 18**   
We require that users between the ages of 13 and 18 ask their parents or legal guardian for permission before using our Service or posting any information on Chatwing.   
Changes to this Policy Please note this Privacy Policy may change from time to time. Any new version or updates will be posted on this page. If you have any additional questions, please contact us. 

May 17, 2015
